축하합니다.
Congratulations.
엘리트 작전 부대의 일원으로 뽑히셨습니다
You've been selected for
an elite operations unit.
괜찮다면 임무 수행이 가능한지
With your permission,
we'd like to conduct a test
결정하기 위해 테스트를 하려고 합니다
to determine your
suitability for service.
네. 근데 왜 하필 절 뽑은거죠?
Sure. You mind me asking
what you're testing me for?
맘 편히 가지세요
Just relax.
모든 것을 알려드릴
훈련용 비디오가 있습니다
We have a short training video
that will explain everything.
잠시만요
Wait.
괜찮아요, 척?
Are you okay, Chuck?
아뇨.. 안 괜찮아요
Oh, um... no, no.
에멧이 하루 종일
로맨틱 코미디를 틀어놔서요
Not since Emmett started
playing romantic comedies 24/7.
"반드시 개를 사랑해야 해요"
영화 Must love dogs의 대사
He must love Must Love Dogs,
하루종일 틀어놓는다니까요
'cause that's always playing.
그렇군요
Right.
오늘 밤은 어떻게 하나 해서요
Well, I was just
wondering about tonight.
오늘 밤에 임무 있어요?
Oh, is there a mission tonight?
아뇨, 발렌타인데이니까
어떻게 해야 하나 싶어서요
Actually, I was referring
to the whole Valentine's Day thing.
아 맞다 그렇지
Oh, my gosh, right.
정말 미안해요?
뭐하고 싶은거 있었어요?
I'm so sorry... did you
want to do something?
아뇨, 아니예요
그냥 궁금해서요
No, no, I was just curious.
척이 하고 싶은게 없다면요
Unless you wanted to do something?
꼭 우리가 뭐 해야하고 그런건 아니죠?
Doesn't it seem like we
ought to do something?
- 새라 맘이잖아요
- 네, 그렇죠
I mean, it's up to you. Yeah, sure.
우리 사귀는 척 한지
이제 1년 넘었잖아요, 맞죠?
Okay, I mean, we have been cover dating
for over a year now, right?
네, 뭘 안하는게 이상할거예요
Yeah, I mean, it would be
weird if we didn't do something.
진짜 이상하겠죠
Completely weird.
오늘 밤엔 사귀는 척
안해도 될지도 몰라요
Maybe we could give our
covers the night off.
안 그래도 처리할 서류가 많아요
I have a bunch of paperwork
to catch up on anyway.
잘됐네요 / 좋아요
Good. Great.
안녕, 안녕
둘 다 발렌타인데이 잘 보내
Hey, hey, hey, happy
Valentine's Day, you two.
오늘 둘이 데이트하지?
Any hot plans for today?
응, 당연하지
Absolutely, there is.
우리 집에서 8시 맞죠?
My house at 8:00, right?
빨리 8시가 됐으면 좋겠네요
I can hardly wait.
그럼 그 때 봐요
I'll see you then, sweetie.
네
Oh, okay.
잘가요
Bye.
우리가 발렌타인데이에 이렇게
Did you ever think that the two of us
현명하고 아름답고 성적으로 대담한
would wind up with smart, beautiful,
여성들과 함께 할거라고 상상이나 해봤어?
sexually adventuresome
girls on Valentine's Day?
내 대답은 아니라는거야
The answer is no.
자네들같은 멍청이들이
Two jackasses like you
섹시한 애나랑 금발하고
사귄단 말이야?
landing two hot pieces
like Anna and Blondie?
정말 말도 안되는 잔인한 일이야
It's a cruel trick of nature.
그라임즈! 내가 발로 차버리기 전에
Grimes! Get your butt to the sales floor
얼른 가서 일 시작해
before I kick it over there.
바토스키
Bartowski,
네 친구들은 어딨어
herd up your nerds.
저기, 저쪽에 있어요
They're right... they're right there.
너희 멍청이 둘은
And you two dimwits,
수리 들어온거 다 고치기 전엔
don't leave the cage until that backlog
퇴근할 생각 마
of repairs are finished.
에밋은 또 어디간거야?
And where is Milbarge?
안녕하세요
Hello.
늦어서 죄송해요
이거 식는거 기다리느라 늦었어요
I'm sorry I'm late... I was
just waiting for these to cool.
대체 그게 뭐야?
What the hell is that?
매니저님 드리려고
컵케익 만들었어요
Oh, well, I put little lips
on the cupcakes for you.
난 자네 머리 위에
얹어놓은거 얘기하는거야
I'm talking about that
thing on your head.
헨리에타가 온다고 해서
Well, Henrietta's in town.
멋있게 보이고 싶어서요
I wanted to look my best.
왜 그래요, 별로 달라진 것도 없는데
I mean, it's not that
much of a difference.
정말 그렇게 생각해요?
Really?
난 내 사무실에 있지
I'll be in my office.
다음부턴 베이킹은
자네 시간에 따로 하게
Next time, do your
baking on your own time.
왜 저래, 누가 초콜렛에
똥이라도 싸뒀대요?
My God, who crapped in
his box of chocolates?
얼마가 들든 상관없어!
I don't care what it costs!
내일까지 가져와!
Get it here tomorrow!
사무실에서 뭐하는거지?
What's he doing in there?
몰라, 빅마이크답지 않아
I don't know, but it's
completely unnatural.
설마..
Oh, my God.
혹시 지금 마이크가..
You don't think that he's...
일하는거 아니냐고?
정신차려, 모건
Working? Calm down, Morgan.
그래, 그것보다 말 되는
Yeah, there's got to be
다른 이유가 있을거야
a rational explanation for this.
아니, 저기 좀 봐
Oh, no, look at him.
꼭 기계같잖아
The guy's a machine.
모건이 뭔가 알고 있는거 같애
I think Morgan's on to something.
진짜 빅 마이크가 아니라면?
What if it's not really Big Mike?
뭐?
What?
미래에서 온 로봇이라도 된단 말이야?
Like, a robot sent from the future?
사이보그
A cybernetic organism.
복제인간
A skin job.
확인할 방법은 한가지 뿐이지
There's only one way to find out.
피가 나면, 사람인거야
If he bleeds, he's human.
얘들아
Guys.
그냥 내가 가서 물어볼게
How about I just talk to him?
Please.
그래 알았어
Okay, fine.
넌 이제 죽었다, 바토스키
It's your funeral, Bartowski.
뭐 하나 물어보지
Let me ask a question, Bartowski.
발렌타인데이 같은 날에
What kind of woman
이혼 서류를 보내는 여자는 대체 뭐지?
delivers divorce papers
on Valentine's Day?
사모님께서 보내셨어요?
Your... your wife?
이제 내 부인도 아니야
The lady Big Mike is no more.
정말 유감이네요, 마이크
I'm-I'm so sorry to hear that, sir.
그러게 말이야
Damn straight.
내 인생 최고의 행운이었는데
놓치고 말았어
I had the catch of a
lifetime and let her get away.
말벗 필요하세요?
You want to talk about it?
아니 괜찮을거야
I'll be fine.
계속 일하다보면
내가 앞으로
Long as I keep working,
I won't have time
홀로 외롭게
사랑도 못 받으며 살아야한다는걸
to realize I'm gonna
spend the rest of my life
잊을 수 있겠지
alone and unloved.
사실 자네가 날 도와줄 일이 있어
There is one thing you can do for me.
네
Sure.
저기 저능아들한테
빨리 일하라고 해
Tell those imbeciles out
there to get cracking!
지금 당장부터
'Cause from now on,
새로운 바이모어가 될거니까
it's a whole new Buy More!
망할 개를 사랑합시다 부터 꺼
Get that damn Must Love Dogs off the TV.
뭐 하나 물어봐도 돼요? / 네
Can I ask you a question? Sure.
이런 지루한 발렌타인데이가
또 있을까요?
This is the worst
Valentine's Day ever, right?
그렇게 나쁘진 않아요
Come on, don't be silly.
괜찮아요, 기분 안 나빠할게요
Please, you're not going to offend me.
그래도 어딘가에 훨씬 재미없게
보내는 사람도 있을거예요
There's got to be someone somewhere
having a far worse Valentine's Day.
1965년 8월 12일 밤
On the night of August 12, 1965,
3연대, 2대대 소속 해병들은
the 2nd Battalion, 3rd Marines
엘리펀트 골짜기에 위험한
헬리콥터 강습 작전을 펼쳤습니다
endeavored to make a
daring helicopter assault
on the Elephant Valley.
내가 방해한게 아니었음 좋겠군
I hope I'm not interrupting.
무슨 일이시죠, 장군님?
What can I do for you, General?
LA 경찰에서 우리 쪽 요원
한 사람을 발견했네
LAPD just picked up one of ours.
이름은 짐 예이거
The agent's name is Jim Yeager.
지난 1년간 실종 상태였는데
He's been missing for over a year,
국내에서 기밀 임무를
수행하고 있다고 알고 있었지
although he was presumed to be
on a covert domestic assignment.
하지만 우리 쪽엔 아무런 기록이 없고
Unfortunately, we have no
record of this assignment,
지금까지 그 요원은..
and so far, the subject has been...
협조를 안 하는군
uncooperative.
입을 다물고 있군요?
Cat's got his tongue, huh?
그니까 입을 열게 하라는 말씀이신가요?
You want me to take a crack at him?
여기 보이듯이, 이미 정신적으로
충분히 쇠약해져 있네
As you can see, his mental
state is fragile enough already.
전화 추적 결과
마지막으로 있었던 장소는
The subject's last confirmed
location comes from a phone call
LA의 한 주택 단지야
traced to this
LA cul-de-sac.
저런데서 살았대요?
Yeager was living in the Valley?
안 미친게 이상하겠네요
Huh... no wonder he went nuts, right?
우리도 그 쪽에 작전 기지로
We took the liberty of
purchasing a home there
쓰기 위해 집을 사뒀다네
to serve as a base of operations.
장군님, 확대 좀 해주시겠습니까
Zoom in on that, please.
계속 뭐라고 하는 것 같은데요?
What's that he keeps saying?
도롱뇽이라고 하는거야
Salamander.
적과 연락할 때 쓰는
암호명인 것 같네
Possible code name
for his enemy contact.
우린 그 근처에
Our best guess: he chose this location
적이 살고 있다고 생각하네
for its proximity to a sleeper cell.
이번 임무는 예이거의 임무를
다시 시작해서
I need for someone to
resume Yeager's assignment,
연락책이 누군지 알아내고
identify his contact
그들의 테러 조직에 잠입하는거네
and infiltrate their terrorist network.
제가 어떻게
거길 잠입해야할지 모르겠습니다
I don't know how well I'd fit
in with those people, General.
자네 말고, 케이시 소령
Not you, Major Casey.
커플이 해야하는 일이야
We need a normal couple.
케이시에요?
That Casey?
임무가 생겼나본데요
Looks like we got a mission.
살았다
Thank God.
안타깝지만 이번 임무 때문에
가짜 데이트를
I'm afraid you two are gonna
have to drop your dating cover
잠시 중단해야겠어
for this particular assignment.
괜찮아 / 무슨 일이예요?
No problem. What is it?
질주하는 갱단?
아님 우크라이나 매춘 조직?
Thai street racing gang, a
Ukrainian prostitution ring?
아니, 이번 임무에선
No, for this mission,
너희 둘이 부부가 되어야해
you and Agent Walker
are gonna be married.
이번엔 교외로 나갈거야
You two kids are going to the suburbs.
둘이서 잘해봐
Good luck as a normal couple.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
영어자막
www.shooter.cn
한글자막
김호정(hojeong_@nate.com)
수정금지 배포자유
안 돼
No.
얜 좀 괜찮네
Maybe.
아빠 셔츠 입으려고?
Breaking out a dad shirt, huh?
응
Yeah.
이거 어때?
What do you think?
그건 너무 나이 들어 보여
Well, I think it makes
you look very grown-up.
잘됐다, 그게 바로 내 목적이야
Oh, good, that's kind of the idea.
둘이 어디 가는데?
Yeah, where are you guys going?
새라랑 나랑 집 봐주러 가는거야
Uh, Sarah and I are just house-sitting.
요거트 가게 사장님이
잠시 집을 비우셨거든
Her boss at the Orange
Orange is out of town, so...
척, 정말 잘됐다
Oh, Chuck, that's... that's great.
교외에서 일주일 푹 쉬는거?
Spending a week in the suburbs?
맞아, 소원 성취 하는거지
Yeah, dream come true.
아니, 그 소리가 아니고
No, don't you get it?
이건.. 이건 예행연습 같은거야
This is... this is like
a dry run, you know,
너랑 새라랑 어떻게 될지 말이야
so you and Sarah can see
what it would really be like.
그만!
Zip it!
결혼하고 싶어 하는 마음은
That is your wedding craziness
거기 누나 맘 속에
고이 간직해
right there, so keep
that... that's yours.
그냥 집 보러 가는거래도
별거 아니야
We're just house-sitting...
it's no big deal.
그래 알았어
그럼 중 2때 부터
Okay, fine, can we call it cohabitating
걸어 놓은 포스터가 없는 곳에서 오래 사귄 여자친구랑
with your long-term
girlfriend in a house
잠시동안 동거하는거라고
부르는건 괜찮지?
that doesn't have posters that
were hung in the eighth grade?
저건..
That-That...
수집품이잖아
아무튼 그래
is a collectible, but yeah, fine.
그렇게 부르는건 괜찮아
We can... we can call it that.
둘이 큰 발전한거야
Then, that is a big step forward.
집이 예쁘네요
Love what you've done with the place.
고마워요, 도움 좀 받았어요
Thanks... I had help.
미안한데 이게 다 뭐예요?
Uh, sorry, but whose
life have I stepped into?
지금 뭐하는거예요?
What-What...
What are you doing?
뭐하는 것 같아요?
What does it look like I'm doing?
감자 샐러드 만들잖아요
I'm making potato salad.
새라가 이웃들 주려고
만들고 있는거예요?
Are you cooking for
the entire neighborhood?
아뇨 척
No, Chuck.
당신이 만들어요
You are.
고기를 그렇게 잘 구우신다면서요
Hey, there's the grill-meister!
환영해요 이웃 사촌~
Welcome, neighbors.
잊지 마요, 저들 중 하나가
Don't forget, one of our new neighbors
우리가 찾고 있는 테러리스트예요
is a suspected terrorist.
얘기 들었지
You heard the little lady.
가서 친해져봐
Get out there and mingle.
얘들아
Gentlemen,
너희들도 다 내 말에
동의할거라고 생각해
I think that I speak
for all of us when I say
내가 여기 바이모어에서 일하는건
that the only reason that I
took this job at the Buy More
여기선 일을 다른 곳 보다
적게 할 수 있다는 점 때문이었어
was to do as little
work as humanly possible.
마이크... 마이크 덕에
다 그게 가능했던거였어
And the big man... he
made that dream a reality.
전 세계 게으름뱅이에게
신적인 존재지
That man's an inspiration
to slackers everywhere.
사모님이 헤어지자고 하기 전까진..
Until his old lady dumped him.
망했어 이제
큰일났다고
We're screwed... I mean, we're screwed
이제 마이크한테 남은거라곤
일 밖에 없잖아
now that he has nothing to
live for except for work.
그래, 그치만 우리가
우리가 뭘 어떻게 돕겠어?
Yeah, but how do we get Mrs.
Big Mike to take him back?
상처받은 마음을 어떻게 치유해주지?
How do you mend a broken heart?
어떻게 여자를 만나게 해주느냐는거죠?
You mean, how do we get him laid?
여러분의 대화를 방해해서 미안하군요
I'm sorry to interrupt this
little meeting of the minds,
하지만 지금 이 상황이 마음에 안드는건
but you're not the only ones
여러분들 뿐만이 아니예요
who find this new regime insufferable.
우리의 덩치 큰 매니저님이
It's obvious that our rotund leader
섹스 못해서 남는 힘을
모두 바이모어에 쏟고 있어요
is channeling his sexual
energies into the Buy More.
내 생각엔, 유일한 희망은..
In my opinion, our only hope...
다시 섹스로 관심을 돌리는거죠
네, 좋은 생각이예요
Is to channel them back
into sex. Yes, brilliant,
하지만 마이크를 좋아해 줄
Emmett, but where do we find
섹시한 여자를 대체 어디서 찾아요?
Big Mike a ridiculously
out of his league hottie?
맞아, 일할 의욕을 없애버릴 정도의
Yeah, someone who will suck his...
그런 여잘 어떻게 찾아
will to work out of him.
베니건스 바엔 없어
Not at a Bennigans's bar.
거긴 가끔 물이 너무 안 좋아
Sometimes, that fruit
hangs a little too low.
돈 안 주고도 섹스할 수 있는
여잔 어디서 만나요?
Where do you meet people you
don't have to pay for sex?
우리 마을에 오신걸 환영해요
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Oh...
안녕하세요
Hi. How you doing?
네 안녕하세요
찰스라고 합니다
I'm good. I'm... I...
Hi. My name is Charles.
전 브래드예요
Oh, I'm Brad.
바로 옆집에 살아요
여기요
I live next door. There you go.
죄송해요
명함이 다 떨어졌네요
I'm... I'm so sorry.
I just ran out.
운이 좋으시네요
제가 명함 만들거든요
Well, lucky for you, I'm
in the stationery biz.
여기 요 녀석 보세요
Check this baby out.
두꺼운 종이에, 새 디자인이고요
It is 110 pound card stock, brand-new,
직접 세공하고
genuine embossing,
앤틱풍으로 마감했죠
antique finish.
다른 사람한테는 말하지 마세요
Listen, don't let any
of these bums know,
내가 원가로 해드릴게
but I can get you a
thousand of those at cost.
일 얘긴 그만 하죠
Enough shoptalk.
저기 가서 사람들 소개시켜 줄게요
괜찮죠?
Let's go meet some of the
natives. What do you say?
그럼요
Okay.
여러분, 찰리예요
Guys, this is Charlie.
찰리, 이 쪽은 마크고요
Uh, Charlie, over here we got Mark.
안녕하세요 / 뭘하든간에
Hi. Hi. Whatever you do,
절대로 이 친구한테
골프 카트 운전을 맡기지 마세요
do not let him drive your golf cart.
이 친구는 데니스고요
데니스와 이 친구 아내
We got Dennis here.
Uh, Dennis and his wife,
트루디는 매주 금요일 밤마다
Trudy, every Friday night,
제스처 게임을 해요
they play a pretty
wild game of charades.
기인들이 따로 없다니까요
It gets pretty zany.
그리고 여기,
가장 중요한, 미치예요
And this one, last but least, Mitch.
이 자식이 말하는건
절대 믿지 마세요
Do not believe a word this dog says.
잠깐
Hold on a minute.
저기 우리 집사람이랑 말하는 사람 누구야?
Who is that talking to my wife?
제 와이프예요
Oh, that's-that's my wife.
새라요
That's Sarah.
Well...
좋겠어요, 찰리
Well done, Charlie.
가끔 한번씩 바꿀래요?
You want to trade sometime?
농담이예요
I'm kidding!
사친회에서 알면 난리날 얘기지
No way the PTA would stand for that.
자 이제 됐어요
All right, all right.
몇 가지만 더 쓰면
데이트 할 수 있어요
Just a few more details
and you will be ready
to mingle with the singles.
근데 랜도 칼리시안이 누구야?
Who the hell is this Lando Calrissian?
세상에서 제일 멋진 사람이요
He's only the coolest guy
in the entire universe.
그냥 사용자명이에요
It's just your user name.
185cm에 84kg?
Six-two, 185 pounds?
이래도 되는거야? / 매니저님
I don't know, Morgan. Listen to me.
다들 온라인에선
키 늘리고 몸무게 줄이고 그래요
Everybody is taller and thinner online.
이렇게 해야 사람들이 관심을 갖죠
It's called the Internet
hotness conversion factor.
직업은 뭘로 하실래요?
What do you want your job to be?
바이모어 매니저
Uh, manager at the Buy More.
우주 비행사라고 해
Make him an astronaut.
- 사자 조련사는 어때?
- 기다려봐, 내가 알아서 할게
What about lion tamer?
Wait, I got it. I got it.
난 아직도 인터넷인지 뭔지를 잘 모르겠어
I just don't know about this whole
World Wide Web business.
어떻게 이걸로 여자를 만나
That ain't no way to meet a woman.
우리 집사람을 어떻게 만났는지 아나?
You know how I met my wife?
교회 소풍에서였어
Church picnic.
그래서 지금 어떻게 끝났나 보세요
Yeah, look how that worked out.
내 자신이나 감정을
숨기진 않았다고
There was no hiding who
you were or-or how you felt.
처음으로 글래디스를
The very first time
보는 순간 바로 알았다고
I laid my eyes on Gladys, I knew.
세상에나
Good Lord.
누구야?
Who are they?
Mm-hmm,
mm-hmm.
매니저님 프로필에 맞는 사람들이예요
Users who matched your profile.
교회 소풍하고는 차원이 다르구만
This ain't no church picnic.
여기 ID, Red Hot Mama 보세요
Check out Red Hot Mama.
섹시한데
Muy caliente.
이 사람도 거짓말 한거 아니야?
What about the Internet
hotness conversion factor?
나도 했는데 아니란법 있어?
Doesn't that work both ways?
저 여자 얼굴은 못 보는거야?
Why can't you see her
face in that picture?
몸매에 집중해요, 마이클
Focus on the body, Michael.
왜 이래요, 마이크
Gee whiz, Mike.
지금 사랑 찾는걸
도와주고 있잖아요
We're trying to help you find love here.
음란하고 음탕한 사랑을
Dirty, nasty, filthy love.
그래서 그리스 사람이 말했지
So, then the Greek guy says,
"뭐 그래도 올리브가
어디로 갔는지는 알잖아"
"Well, at least we know
where the olive went."
저랑 똑같은 생각하시는군요
My sentiments exactly.
제가 비밀 하나 알려줄까요? 성함이..
Can I let you in on little a secret
about your neighbors, Mr...?
찰스 카마이클입니다
Carmichael. Charles.
다들 재미없는 사람들이에요
They bore me.
그래요?
Oh, yeah?
네, 뭐..
Yeah, it's, uh...
별로 재밌진 않네요
it's not really my scene either.
우리 둘이 가끔씩 같이 놀아요
Perhaps the two of us can,
uh, get together sometime.
우리 둘이서 조금 더..
Maybe engage in
something a little more...
자극적으로
stimulating?
저기, 잠시만..
Don't-Don't...
죄송해요
미끄러워서..
Sorry. I... Slippery.
제안은 정말 감사해요
That's very kind of you to offer
재밌을 것 같긴 하지만
and it sounds like a lot of fun,
전 지금 막 결혼했거든요
but I am very, very married.
축하해요, 카마이클씨
Congratulations, Mr. Carmichael.
저도 마찬가지예요
But who isn't?
제 남편도 저기 있어요
My husband's right over there.
덩치가 크시네요
He's a big fella, isn't he?
무슨 일 하시는 분이세요?
What line of work is he in?
벌목?
Lumberjack?
자주 집을 비우는 일이요
The kind that keeps him out of town.
찰스!
Charles!
부인이예요?
Is that your wife?
꽤나..
She seems very...
미인이네요
pretty.
전 이만 가봐야겠네요
Well, got to run. You know how it is.
아내가 부르면 달려가야죠
ball and chain : 아내
The old ball and chain.
저기, 찰스
Listen, Charles.
전 바로 길 건너 살아요
I just live right across the street.
신혼 재미가 끝나거든 전화해주세요
So call me... when the honeymoon's over.
저도 사슬(Chain) 있어요
I've got a chain, too.
네 그러시겠죠
I bet you do.
잠시만요
Excuse me.
어때요?
Well?
아무것도 없어요
전혀요
No flashes. No nothing.
우리 이웃들은 이상 없는 것 같아요
I think our neighbors are clean.
길 건너 사는 부인 빼고요
Except for that lady across the street.
자꾸 실례되는 말만 해요
She's got a dirty mouth.
모든 사람 다 확인해본거 맞아요?
Well, are you sure
you checked everybody?
이 동네가 아닐지도 몰라요
Maybe we got the
wrong cul-de-sac.
저기요
Mr. and Mrs. Carmichael?
잠시 안으로 와주시겠어요?
Would you come inside, please?
케이블에 문제가 있어요
There's a slight
problem with your cable.
우리 쪽 물건 같은데
Looks like one of ours.
아뇨
지금은 아니에요
Uh, correction... that was one of ours.
CIA 오마하 지국에서
도난당한 도청기예요
That bug was stolen from
a CIA substation in Omaha
2006년에요
in '06.
지금은 풀크럼 쪽 물건이고요
Now it belongs to FULCRUM.
그냥 평범한 테러리스트를
상대하는줄 알았는데
And here I thought
we were all looking for a
garden-variety terrorist.
빨리 나와봐요
Better hurry up, buddy.
소시지가 타고 있어요
Your wieners are burning.
저 사람들 꼴보기도 싫어
I knew these people creeped me out.
척, 잘 잤어요?
Hi. Did you sleep well?
잘 잤어요, 여보
Like a log, honey.
자긴 잘 잤어요?
How did you sleep?
뭐하는거예요?
케이시가 도청기 또 찾았어요?
What are you doing? Did
Casey find more bugs?
그냥 아침하는거에요
I'm cooking breakfast.
케이시가 다 확인했어요
아무것도 없어요
Casey swept the house. It's clean.
그럼 누구 초대했어요?
Okay. Well, are we going to
invite the neighbors over?
아뇨, 당신 주려고 만드는거예요
No, Chuck. I-I'm cooking for you.
왜요?
What?
아니예요
Nothing.
재밌어서요
It's just funny.
이런 모습은 생각 안해봤거든요
I never pictured you doing this.
그랬어요?
Well, what can I say?
제가 잘하는게 많답니다
I'm versatile.
앉아요
Sit.
잠깐
Hold on.
정말 가정 주부 역할 하는걸
즐기고 있는거예요?
Are-Are-Are
you enjoying
this whole Martha Stewart thing?
믿기지가 않아요
I can't believe it.
갑자기 왜 이렇게
부드럽게 굴고 그래요
Please tell me you're
not going soft on me.
입 다물고 아침이나 먹어요
Just shut up and eat your breakfast.
조심해요, 새라
You better be careful, Sarah.
그러다 진짜 여자 되겠어요
One day you might actually
turn into a real girl.
여보
Sweetie.
Sweetie?
깜빡할 뻔 했네요
I almost forgot.
퇴근 길에 잠시 가게 좀 들러줄래요?
Would you mind swinging
by the store for me?
좋은 하루 보내요
Have a great day at work.
그럴게요
Okay.
그 표정 집어 치워
Wipe that look off your face.
이리 줘요, 그거 새라가..
Wait, that's Sarah's...
안 보이는 잉크로 썼어요?
Invisible ink, really? You guys can't
그냥 전화로 하면 안돼요?
지금 상대하는건 풀크럼이야
just use the phone? We're
dealing with FULCRUM here.
집하고 전화, 모두 도청한다고
They bugged your house,
they bugged the phones.
이렇게 예전 방식으로
해야 할 때도 있는거야
Sometimes you got to do
it the old-fashioned way.
위치 확인, 표적 이동 중?
"Location clear. Target on move"?
잠깐, 그럼 누가 도청기를
심은건지 알아낸거예요?
Wait. You guys figured
out who planted the bug?
응
Yeah.
인터섹트가 아무 말 안해주디?
Ring any Intersect bells?
이 사람, 미친 아줌마 남편이잖아요
Yeah, that's crazy
cougar lady's husband.
이 사람인건 어떻게 알았어요?
How do you know it's him?
너랑 새라가 집에서 노느라 바쁠 때
Well, while you and Walker
were busy playing house,
난 예전 방식대로
일을 좀 했거든
I was doing some
old-fashioned spy work.
도청기에서 지문이 발견돼서
Pulled a fingerprint off the bug,
데이터 베이스에 검색해봤어
ran it through the database.
풀크럼에 들어가기 전에 어떤 사람이었어요?
So, who was this guy before FULCRUM?
CIA 심리 작전 부대
CIA Psy-Ops.
정신과 의사 단체 같은거야
정신병자 천국이지
Agency shrinks. A real bunch of weirdos.
은행 기록도 조회해봤어
I also ran his bank records.
여기서 가디나 거리 만큼이나
이걸 사뒀더라고
Turns out he bought enough of this stuff
to stretch from here to Gardena.
인피니밴드 데이터 라인이라고
우리가 기관 인트라넷에
Infiniband data line.
The same stuff we use
접근할 때 쓰는거랑 똑같은거야
to tap into the Agency's intranet.
네 이웃이 이게 왜 필요했을까?
Any idea what your
neighbor was using it for?
글쎄요
I don't know.
온라인 게임?
Uh, online gaming?
포르노?
Porn?
또? / 몰라요
Or... I don't know. Or...
정부 서버를 해킹하는데 썼겠지
Hacking into government servers.
정부 서버를 해킹한다
Or hacking into government servers.
안 그래도 그 얘기 하려고 했어요
I was going to say that eventually.
어쨌든 잘됐어요
해결했다니 다행이네요
Okay, great. I'm glad
you guys cracked it.
내가 도움이 됐다니 다행이네요
Glad I could help.
그래
Help...
그 집에 들어가서
컴퓨터에 접근해봐
by getting us into that
house and onto that computer.
컴퓨터 고치러 가라는거예요?
You want me to go in as Nerd Herd?
또 틀렸어, 바토스키
Wrong again, Bartowski.
예전 방식대로 해야지
You're going to go in
the old-fashioned way.
실비아랑 자라고요?
You want me to sleep
with our neighbor Sylvia?
아니
자고 싶어하는 척만 하라는거지
No, we want you to pretend
to want to sleep with her,
가서 그 여자 남편 컴퓨터에
접근하란 말이야
and then see if you can get
on her FULCRUM husband's PC
뭐 떠오르는게 있나 보라고
and see if you flash on anything.
덤으로 섹스도 하고 싶다면야..
You want to throw in a little sex...
그건 네 맘대로 해
that's your prerogative.
됐고요, 케이시
내가 그렇게 하면
Whatever, Casey. Look, I just don't know
새라가 어떻게 생각할지 모르겠어요
how Sarah's going to feel about this.
자기 남편이 다른 여자랑
There's no way she's
잔다는데 그걸 어떻게 두고 보겠..
going to let her husband
just sleep with...
척 준비됐대?
Is he ready?
척, 미안해요
하지만 이거 말곤 방법이 없어요
Chuck, look, I'm sorry,
but this is our best option.
그 자가 집에 최첨단의
보안 시설을 설치해뒀어
Target's got the house rigged
with state-of-the-art security.
마침 그 남자 부인이
너한테 관심이 있다고 하니까..
And since his wife's expressed
a romantic interest in you...
그 점을 이용해달라는거예요
We need you to exploit it.
이용해달라, 알겠어요
Oh, exploit it. Gotcha.
CIA는 항상 그런식이죠
Yeah. Textbook CIA.
척, 케이시랑 내가
계속 지켜볼거예요
Look, Casey and I will be
with you every step of the way.
그래, 아줌마가 이상하게 나오면
Yeah, if the cougar gets a little hairy,
바로 빠져나와
you can always tap out.
이번 임무가 불편할거라는거 알아요
Look, we understand
if this makes you uncomfortable.
가짜 결혼 서약을 어기는거요?
Breaking my fake wedding vows?
아뇨, 괜찮아요
No, forget about it.
내가 운이 좋은거죠
향수나 한번 더 뿌려줘요
I'm golden. Just hit
me with another spritz
of that, would you?
여긴 왜 뿌려요?
Why here?
카마이클씨
Mr. Carmichael.
이렇게 빨리 오실줄은 몰랐는걸요
I didn't expect you to come so quickly.
찰스 카마이클은 항상 빠르답니다
Charles Carmichael always comes quickly.
조심해, 바토스키
Real smooth, Bartowski.
들어오세요 / 네
Come on in. Okay.
케이블이 위층 북서쪽 방향으로 들어가
The cable enters the house
through the northwest corner, upstairs.
오 이런
Oh, hey!
여기가 굉장한 일이 벌어지는 곳이군요
This is where the magic happens.
여기 이러고 있는걸 당신 부인이 알면
What do you think
your, uh, wife would say
뭐라고 할 것 같아요?
if she knew you were up here?
질투할까요?
You think she'd be jealous?
전에 말씀하셨던것처럼
Well, it's like you said.
신혼이잖아요..
I mean, the honeymoon...
질투하겠죠
she is over.
이런거 물어봐도 모르겠는데
Hi-oh. If you don't mind me asking,
둘이 마지막으로
사랑을 나눈게 언제였어요?
when was the last time you
and your wife made love?
글쎄요
Well, that's a...
그게.. 음..
that's a... that's a...
좋은 질문이네요
That's a good one.
요즘 들어 우리 부부가
You know, things have been a little cold
- 그 쪽으론 별로 좋지가 않았거든요
- 저런 불쌍해라
in that department
lately. Oh, poor baby.
내가 지금부터 뭘 할지 알아요, 찰스?
Do you know what I'm going
to do to you, Charles?
네, 알 것 같아요
I got a pretty good idea.
내가 당신을 녹여줄게요
I'm going to thaw you out.
당연히 그러시겠죠
Oh, I bet you are,
왜 이러세요
you-you
she-devil.
성격이 급하시네요
양말까지 벗기시고
You temptress, you've taken my sock off.
간지러워요 간지러워요
Ticklish. Ticklish. Ticklish.
발 조심하세요
간지러워요
Those are my feet. That's my feet area.
음 저기 있잖아요?
Maybe-Maybe you know what?
우선 잠깐 얘기부터 하는게 어때요?
Maybe we could just
talk for a few minutes.
네? 어때요?
How's that sound? Ugh.
얘기하러 오신게 아니잖아요
You didn't come here to talk.
그랬나요? 얘기하러 온게 아니였어요?
I didn't? I didn't come here to talk?
왜요? 대화가 어디가 어때서요
Why, why not? Talking's perfectly...
다들 대화가 대단한 일인줄 알아요, 그쵸?
Talking's overrated anyway, isn't it?
잠깐, 저기요
No, you know what?
제가 지금 조금..
It's just that I'm a little...
조금 긴장한 것 같아요
I'm a little nervous because this is...
이런 불륜을 저지르는게
the whole adultery game is
저한텐 익숙치가 않아서요
a little new... little new to me.
제 생각에는요
뭐라도 마시면
And I think, I think
just a... just a drink,
뭐라도 마시면
괜찮아질 것 같아요
a little liquid courage would
really go a long way right now.
스카치 갖다줄까요?
Is Scotch okay?
그거 좋겠네요
Sounds delish.
고마워요
Thank you.
전 여기 있을게요
I'll be right here.
이렇게 묶어두셨으니까요
But you already knew that.
미친 아줌마
Crazy person.
이게 뭐야
Come...
케이시, 수갑 채웠어요
Casey, I'm handcuffed.
진정해, 빠져나오기 쉬워
Relax. Handcuffs are a cinch.
그래요? / 응
Really? Yeah.
엄지 손가락 보면 작은 뼈가 있을거야
There's a bone in your thumb. Tiny bone.
작아서 부러뜨리기 쉬워
Real easy to break.
어떻게 하는 거냐면
What you're gonna want
to do is you're gonna
딱 소리가 날때까지
꾹 누르면 돼
want to apply torsional
pressure to it until it snaps.
뼈를 부러뜨리긴 싫어요
I'm not gonna break my bone!
그럼 방법 없어
Well, in that case, you are screwed.
생각해, 생각해봐
Think. Think. Think.
잠깐
Wait a minute. Wait.
그렇지
Hey.
그래 이거야
Hey. Hey.
그렇지
Oh, okay.
젠장, 비밀번호 걸어놨어
Damn it. Password protected.
도롱뇽이네
Salamander.
척
Chuck.
척, 빨리 빠져나와요
Chuck, you have to get out of there.
척, 척
Chuck? Chuck?
그대로 있어
내가 들어갈게
Stay where you are, Agent
Walker. I'm going in after him.
테스트 해봤어?
Have you tested him yet?
위에 있어
수갑 채워놨어
He's upstairs. I've got him cuffed.
방금까진 있었어
He was just here.
테스트 했나봐
He ran the test.
살아 남았어
He survived.
드디어 찾아냈어
We found our subject.
안녕하세요
Good afternoon.
찰리?
Charlie?
브래드
Brad.
방금 무슨 일이 있었는지
상상도 못 할거예요
You are never gonna believe what
just happened to me over there!
이거 재밌겠는데
Well, this ought to be good.
자네들에게 잠입을 했지
I send you there undercover
바토스키를 풀크럼에
일반인들한테까지
and you not only nearly
expose Mr. Bartowski to FULCRUM
노출시키라고 했나?
but to an entire
cul-de-sac of civilians?
면목 없습니다, 장군님
저희가 망쳤습니다
No excuses, General, we pooched it.
아뇨
No.
아니에요, 망치지 않았어요
No, we didn't pooch it.
아니라고요, 장군님
We didn't pooch it. General, look,
컴퓨터에서 뭔가를 봤어요
I-I saw something on
that computer, okay?
여러 장의 사진들이었어요
I saw... pictures.
참 놀랍군 / 장군님
How illuminating. General,
그냥 평범한 사진이 아니었어요
they weren't regular pictures.
인터섹트 같은 사진들이었어요
They were like Intersect pictures,
브라이스가 저한테 보낸 것 같은거요
embedded files, like the ones
that Bryce sent me, only...
아주 다르긴 했지만요
very different.
머리 속에 풀크럼에 대한
정보가 들어간거 같아요
We think Chuck could have
FULCRUM programming in his brain.
그렇다면
In that case,
이번 임무에서 척을 제외시켜야겠어
I'm pulling Mr. Bartowski
from this operation.
워커 요원의 위장이
들통나기 전까지는
But as long as Agent
Walker's cover is intact,
자네 둘은 계속 그 단지에 머물고
I want you two to lock
down the cul-de-sac,
풀크럼 요원을 감시하고
monitor FULCRUM,
우리가 다른 방법을 찾을 때까지
잠입할 수 있는 다른 방법을 찾아보게
see what else you can uncover
before we make a move on their cell.
자네들 부부는 이제 이혼이야
The Carmichaels are getting a divorce.
이런 이런
Oh, my, my, my.
오늘 멋지네요, 마이클
Don't you look prosperous, Michael.
오늘이 그 여자랑
데이트하는 날이군요?
Wow, tonight's the night
with the Internet lady?
기분이 어떠세요?
How ya feeling, big guy?
사기꾼이 된 기분이야
Like an imposter.
날 봐
Look at me.
내 꼴을 보라고
Look at this ridiculous outfit.
날 보자마자 내가 84kg 짜리
She's gonna take one
look at me and realize
선박왕이 아니라는걸 알아차릴거야
I am not a 185-pound shipping magnate.
괜찮아요 양복이 참..
Oh, relax. That suit is...
라인이 살았는데요 / 맞아요
very slimming. That's right.
괜찮아요, 있잖아요
That's right. You know what?
그래서 돈이 많아 보여요
It'll make your wallet look fat.
모건 말이 맞아요
Yeah, Morgan's right.
보는 순간 넋을 잃을거에요
That poor lady is not
gonna know what hit her.
넋을 잃다 못해 쓰러질걸요
You're gonna need a hydraulic
crowbar to pry her off.
맞아
Yes.
자넨 어떻게 생각해?
What do you say, Bartowski?
솔직히 말해야할까?
Should I come clean?
솔직하게 내가 누군지?
Tell her who I really am?
자넨 직업이 뭔지 거짓말 안했어도
You got your girl without having to lie
여자친구 잘만 사겼잖아, 맞지?
about your lowly occupation, right?
그건 그런데..
Um... yeah, you know,
절 역할 모델 삼아도 될지 모르겠네요
I'm-I'm not so sure
I'm the best role model.
여기 이 찌질이들보단 낫잖아
You're better than these losers.
너네가 마지막으로
데이트 해본게 언제야?
When was the last time
any of y'all had dates?
베니건스는 안 쳐줘
And I'm not counting Bennigan's.
그리고 넌 애나랑
2주에 한번씩 헤어지잖아
And you... you and Anna
break up every other week.
그리고 자네
And you...
난 자네는 어디
소속인지조차 모르겠어, 엘비스
I don't even know what
your affiliation is, Elvis.
소속이라니 무슨 말이죠?
What does he mean, my affiliation?
화장실 말이에요
That bathroom thing.
마이크, 전 잘 모르겠어요
Look, Mike, I don't know.
하고 싶은대로 하세요
It's up to you.
하지만 정말 거짓말로 시작된
만남을 하고 싶으세요?
But do you really want to
be a part of a relationship
that's founded on lies?
정답은 "응"이에요
The answer's yes.
- 당연하죠
- 쟤가 제 정신이 아니라 그래요
Yep. Absolutely. He is not thinking.
맙소사
Oh, my...
워커
Agent Walker,
누가 네 쪽으로 가고 있어
I've got unknowns
moving on your position.
새라에요
메시지를 남겨주세요
This is Sarah. Leave a message.
새라, 케이시
빨리 거기서 빠져나와요
Sarah, Sarah, you and Casey
have to get out of the cul-de-sac
어서요! 방금 떠올랐어요
지금 막 생각난건데
immediately... I just flashed,
I just flashed on something.
내 생각엔 풀크럼이랑 관련된 것 같아요
I think it was FULCRUM...
it was something that I...
그 때 그 컴퓨터에서
알게 된 것 같아요
I uploaded off the computer, okay.
실례할게요, 안녕하세요
우리 집 케이블에
Excuse me. Hi. Yeah, could you
문제가 있는 것 같은데
도와주실래요?
give me a hand with my cable, please?
그 동네를 지은 회사로
위장한 거예요
The company that built the
neighborhood is a front.
무료 프리미엄 채널을 원하시는거면
Uh, if you're looking
for free premium channels
다른 사람한테 가보세요
I'm not the guy.
아뇨 그게 아니고요
Oh, no, no, no.
It's nothing like that.
그 집 뿐만이 아니에요
It's not just a house.
그 동네 사람들 전체가 풀크럼이에요
The entire neighborhood is FULCRUM.
왠지는 모르겠는데
For some reason
자꾸 이상하게 연결이 안되네요
I'm getting some kind
of weird interference.
제 생각엔 동네 사람 중에 누가
I think somebody in the neighborhood
might be running some kind
고성능 전기 장치를 쓰는 것 같아요
of high-powered electronic equipment.
사실 제 생각엔 말이죠
Actually, I think it... it might be
저쪽 집 때문인 것 같아요
that house right over there.
안녕하세요
Hi.
남편분 일은 정말 유감이에요
I'm so sorry
about what happened with your husband.
정말 힘드시겠어요
It must have been awful.
이럴 때 일수록 이웃끼리 도와야죠
It's times like these you
need your neighbors most.
고맙습니다
Oh. Thank you.
들어오세요
Uh, come in.
브라우니를 좋아했으면 좋겠네
I hope you like brownies.
부인 찾아요?
Looking for the wife?
지금 숙녀분들하고 대화중이세요
She's having a chat with the ladies.
괜찮아요?
You feeling all right, buddy?
- 혈압은 어때?
- 조금 높아
- How's this blood pressure?
- A little heigh.
진정제를 좀 줄까?
Should I give him more sedative?
아냐 / 새라
No. CHUCK: Sarah?
괜찮아지겠지 / 새라
He's going to be fine. Sarah?
새라는 어딨어요?
Where's Sarah?
새라
Sarah?
새라는 어딨죠?
Where's Sarah?
우리 안사람은 어딨냐고요 / 카마이클
Where's my wife? Mr. Carmichael,
당신 아내 아닌거 다 알아
she isn't your wife.
CIA 요원이지
She's a CIA agent.
당신도 마찬가지고
And so are you.
뭐야
Wha...
나한테 원하는게 뭐냐고
What do you want with me?
자네 머리가 아주 대단하던걸
You have got a very special brain.
걱정마
Don't worry.
손상되지 않게
최대한 노력해볼테니까
We're going to do everything
we can to not damage it.
손상? 손상이라고?
Damage? Damage?
이 사람 뭐라는거야?
What is he talking about?
우리집 2층에서
컴퓨터 프로그램의 일부를 봤잖아
What you saw upstairs was a small part
of a computer program.
CIA에서 암호화된 이미지를 통해
The CIA designed it
요원들에게 정보를 심기 위해
to implant intelligence
directly into agents
고안해낸 프로그램이지
through encoded images.
하지만 나중엔 쓰임이 바뀌었어
But the CIA gave up on the program.
냉전 때 일어났던 테러 전쟁에
They decided to slug it out,
대항하는데에 쓰기로 했거든
fighting the war on terror
using Cold War tactics.
우린 그 프로그램을
But we're training agents
미래의 전쟁에 참여할 요원들을
훈련하는데에 써
who are ready to fight tomorrow's wars.
그 미래의 일부가
되어보지 않겠나?
How would you like to
be a part of that future?
풀크럼 요원이 되는건 어때?
How would you like
to be part of FULCRUM?
새라는..
What about...
새라는 어떻게 되는거지?
What about her?
시키는대로 다 할테니까
새라는 놓아줘
Look, I'll do whatever
you want, just let her go.
설마 파트너를 진심으로 좋아하는거야?
Don't tell me you have feelings
for your partner? Boy,
꽤나 좋아하는 모양이지?
you really let her get
into your head, huh?
쟤가 뭐래?
What did she tell you?
언젠간 둘이 함께 할 수 있을거래?
That someday you two would be together?
여기처럼 예쁜 동네에 둘이 정착해 살자고?
Maybe settle down in a
cute little cul-de-sac
like this one?
웃긴 친구구만
You're funny.
여긴 다 가짜야
This place isn't real.
너에 대한
저 여자의 감정도 마찬가지고
Her feelings for you aren't real.
걱정마
Don't worry.
이번 테스트가
잊는데에 도움이 될거야
This next part should
help you get over her.
살아남는다면 말이지
If he survives it.
척!
Chuck!
못 들어
He can't hear you.
안 돼!
No, no, no!
척...
Chuck... Chuck...
죽었어 / 척
Oh, he's toast. SARAH: Chuck.
치워 버려
Get him out of here.
다른 놈들 갖다 버린 곳에 버려
Dump him where you dumped the others.
어떻게 된거죠?
What just happened?
카마이클
Mr. Carmichael.
여기가 어딘지 알겠어?
Do you know where you
are, Mr. Carmichael?
비밀 작전을 위해 지어진
Beneath Meadow Branch
subdivision in a FULCRUM lab
풀크럼 연구소 미도우 지국 지하
that was built as part
of a secret initiative.
무슨 작전?
What initiative?
인터섹트 컴퓨터를
다시 만드는 작전
To rebuild the Intersect computer.
세상에, 됐어
Oh, my God, it worked.
한 가지 더 물어봐도 될까?
Can I ask just
one more question?
이번엔 당신 아내에게
테스트 해봐도 될까?
You mind if we, uh, test your wife next?
아내라니?
Wife?
난 결혼한 적 없어
I don't have a wife.
테스트를 시작하기 전에
Before you run the test,
워커 요원에게 한마디 해야겠어
I'd like to tell Agent Walker something.
워커 요원이라
Agent Walker.
이제야 이름을 알았네
Now we have a name.
눈 감아요
Close your eyes.
안돼! 안돼!
No, no, no!
괜찮아요?
Are you okay?
네, 척은요?
Yeah. You?
괜찮은 것 같아요
I think so.
다 구치소로 끌고 가
Take these guys to the detention center.
이 놈은 시체 안치실로
That one goes to the agency morgue.
아직 볼 일이 남았으니까
We're not done with him yet.
사람에게 테스트하는걸 보니
Besides testing on humans,
풀크럼 쪽에서 인터섹트 컴퓨터를
it appears that FULCRUM
is perilously close
거의 다 완성한 것 같네
to completing their
own Intersect computer,
즉 바토스키가 더 중요한 인물이 됐어
making Bartowski more
important than ever.
바토스키의 목숨이 위험한 상태야
His life has never been in more danger.
이제 행복한 시간은 끝났네, 워커 요원
The honeymoon is over, Agent Walker.
네 알겠습니다
Yes, ma'am.
새라, 다 괜찮은거죠?
Hey, everything okay?
네, 그냥 평소처럼 보고한거예요
Yeah, just a routine debriefing.
오늘 밤에 그 집에
Uh, so I was wondering
놀러갈 생각 없나 해서요
if you wanted to swing by
the old cul-de-sac tonight.
왜요?
Why?
아니 그게..
Uh, I don't know, I mean, I... you know,
CIA에서 집을 관리하고 있고
I figured we've still got the place,
누나도 우리가 아직
집 보는줄 아니까
and Ellie still thinks
we're house-sitting,
밤에 다시 돌아가서
놀면 좋을 것 같아서요
so I thought that,
you know, we could maybe
enjoy a night in the suburbs,
음식도 주문하고 영화도 빌려서
order in, rent a movie.
임무 걱정도 없이
우리 단 둘이서요
No mission to worry about,
just Mr. and Mrs. Carmichael.
재밌게요 / 척
Maybe have some fun. Chuck,
다시 못 돌아가요
we can't go back there.
그냥 위장일 뿐이었어요
It was just a cover.
네, 나도 알아요
하지만 전 그냥..
Yeah, I know that,
I just thought that...
케이시랑 임무 마무리 짓고 와야해요
Casey and I have to
shut down the operation.
나중에 마저 얘기해도 되죠?
Can we talk later?
그럼요
Absolutely.
척?
Uh, Chuck?
네
Yeah.
그거 다시 돌려주세요
I'm going to need that back.
맞다
Right.
깜빡할 뻔 했네요
Almost forgot.
마이클
Hey.
데이트는 어땠어요?
How was the big date?
정말 최고의 정열적인 밤이었어
Gentlemen, it was a night
of exquisite passion.
상상도 할 수 없는 일을
그 분과 함께 했다니까
I did things with that woman
I didn't even know existed,
- 법 여러 개 어겼어
- 잘하셨어요! 우리 말대로 했죠?
which are likely illegal.
Yes! So you took our advice?
거짓말했어
I lied my ass off.
- 저희가 말씀 드렸잖아요
- 다 그렇게 시작하는거예요
What did we tell you? Way to
get back in the game, chief.
자 이제 그만들 떠들어
시간 낭비 그만해
Enough chitchat. We're burning daylight.
레스터, 넌 너드 허드에 가있고
Lester, man the Nerd Herd desk.
제프, 넌 가서 쟤들 도와줘
Jeff, help out the green shirts.
점심까지 재고 물품 목록 가져와
I want the new inventory
stocked by lunch.
가게를 최대한 깔끔하게 해야해
My store had better be shipshape.
그니까 저희한테 일하라는 말씀이세요?
What, you're making us work?
새 여자친구는 어쩌고요?
What about your new girlfriend?
그게 뭐?
What about her?
곧 여기로 올거야
She's gonna be here any minute.
여기로 초대했어
I invited her down.
Wow.
마이클
Michael,
무슨 일이에요?
what's going on?
왜 옷을 그렇게 입고 있어요?
Why are you dressed like that?
여기서 일하니까요
Because I work here.
저 여기 매니저예요, 볼로니아
I am a manager at the Buy More, Bolonia.
선장님이라고 하셨잖아요
But I thought you were a boat captain.
선박왕 얘긴 다 제가 지어낸 얘기에요
Shipping magnate,
but that was something I just made up
그래야 어제 같은
데이트를 할 수 있을거라 생각했어요
so I could get to do
what we did last night.
하지만 어젯밤 이후로..
But after we did what
we did last night, I...
더이상 당신에게
거짓말 할 수가 없었어요
I can't bear to lie to you anymore,
이제 제가 싫다고 하셔도
다 이해해요
so I'll understand if you want
to tell me where to shove it,
하지만 용서해주셨으면 좋겠어요
but I hope you'll forgive me.
용서할게요
I do forgive you.
사실은..
The truth is
저도 그 프로필에
모두 솔직하게 쓰진 않았어요
I wasn't 100% honest on
my dating profile either.
괜찮아요,
몸무게 좀 줄인거야 상관없어요
Aw, honey, I don't mind
a little extra weight.
저 아들이 있어요
I have a son.
네? 뭐 어때요
Oh, w-well,
s-so what?
저 애들 좋아해요
I love kids.
26살이에요
He's 26 years old.
알고 계신줄 알았어요
I thought you found out.
그래서 여기서 만나자고
하신 줄 알았는데요
I thought that's why you wanted
to meet here in the store.
무슨 말씀이세요
I don't follow.
마이클, 제 아들 여기서 일해요
Michael, my son works here.
세상에 주여
제발 바토스키이길
Please, Lord, let it be Bartowski.
엄마
Mother.
아들
Mi hijo.
Ah, yeah.
아들?
?i hijo?
우리 엄마랑 잤어요?
You're banging my mom?
왔구나
Hey.
내가 뭐랬어?
What did I tell you?
확실히 달라졌지?
House-sitting really
changes things, huh?
그렇더라. 누나가
바라는대로 달라지진 않았지만
Absolutely, just-just not
in the way you were hoping,
누나
El.
솔직히 말해서
To tell you the truth,
나랑 새라한테는 최악이었어
the suburbs were kind of a
disaster for me and Sarah.
왜 그래? 뭐가 잘못된건데?
Well, what happened? What went wrong?
처음 시작부터 잘못된 것 같아
I guess something that's
been wrong from the start.
You know?
그치만 둘이 헤어진건 아니지?
Are... you guys aren't
breaking up, are you?
아냐, 아냐
헤어진건 아니야
No, no, no, no, no, trust me,
Sarah's not going anywhere.
척, 무슨 말인지 잘 못 알아듣겠어
Chuck, I guess I don't...
I don't know what you're saying exactly.
누나가 얼마나 새라를 좋아하는거,
Look, El, I know how much you love Sarah
나랑 새라가 누나네처럼
and I know how much
you love the idea of us
잘되길 간절히 바란다는거 잘 알아
and us moving forward
with you and Devon,
하지만 우린 누나네랑은 달라
but we're not anything like you guys.
너희 둘이 얼마나 잘 어울리는데
But you guys seem so perfect.
그래 나도 알아
하지만 새라랑 같이 지내는게
Yeah, I know, I guess, but
being in that house with her,
항상 내가 꿈꿔왔던 것 처럼
it was so close to being perfect...
너무나도 완벽했지만
the way I had always
pictured it would be...
깨달았어
that I realized
그 꿈에 뭔가 문제가 있다는걸
what was wrong with that picture.
바로 우리가 문제였어
And it was us.
새라랑 난 지금 관계 이상으로
발전하지 않을거야
Sarah and I are never
going to be anything more
than what we are right now.
그리고 있잖아
And you know what?
난 그래도 괜찮아
I'm okay with that.
그렇게 됐어
Anyway...
워커
Agent Walker,
필요한거 다 챙겼지?
you get everything you need?
응
Yeah.
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)
Transcript : yyets.net